var deck = [
    {
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 1,
        "UUID": "6-1-1",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:1, to whom did the Lord speak after the death of Moses?",
        "A": "Joshua",
        "B": "Eleazar",
        "C": "Aaron",
        "D": "Caleb",
        "Correct": "A"
    },
    {
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 2,
        "UUID": "6-1-2",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:1, who was Joshua’s father?",
        "A": "Moses",
        "B": "Nun",
        "C": "Jesse",
        "D": "Achan",
        "Correct": "B"
    },
    {
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 3,
        "UUID": "6-1-3",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:1, in what role did Joshua serve under the leadership of Moses?",
        "A": "Spokesman",
        "B": "General",
        "C": "Assistant",
        "D": "Priest",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
    {
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 4,
        "UUID": "6-1-4",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:2, where did the Lord tell Joshua and all the people to go?",
        "A": "Over the Jordan",
        "B": "Beyond the River Euphrates",
        "C": "To Gilgal",
        "D": "To Acacia Grove",
        "Correct": "A"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 5,
        "UUID": "6-1-5",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:3, what did God say that he had given to Joshua and the children of Israel?",
        "A": "The houses of their enemies ",
        "B": "Every place that the sole of his foot would tread upon",
        "C": "Vineyards and much livestock",
        "D": "Bread from Heaven ",
        "Correct": "B"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 6,
        "UUID": "6-1-6",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:4, which of the following is NOT used by the Lord to describe what would be the territory of Israel?",
        "A": "From the wilderness",
        "B": "All the land of the Hittites",
        "C": "From the River Jordan",
        "D": "To the Great Sea",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 7,
        "UUID": "6-1-7",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:5, who would be able to stand before Joshua?",
        "A": "No king in the land",
        "B": "Eleazar the priest",
        "C": "No man",
        "D": "No Canaanite ",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 8,
        "UUID": "6-1-8",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:6, what had the Lord sworn to their fathers to give them?",
        "A": "Many blessings",
        "B": "The land",
        "C": "Descendants as the stars of heaven",
        "D": "Protection from their enemies",
        "Correct": "B"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 9,
        "UUID": "6-1-9",
        "Question": "According to Joshua 1:7, what did God tell Joshua NOT to do regarding the law which Moses commanded them?",
        "A": "Turn from it ",
        "B": "Desecrate it",
        "C": "Violate it",
        "D": "Fail to remember it",
        "Correct": "A"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 10,
        "UUID": "6-1-10",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:8, what did God say should not depart from Joshua’s mouth?",
        "A": "The song of Moses",
        "B": "The Book of the Law",
        "C": "Manna from Heaven",
        "D": "Praises to God",
        "Correct": "B"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 11,
        "UUID": "6-1-11",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:8, how often was Joshua to meditate in the Book of the Law?",
        "A": "Every day",
        "B": "Every Sabbath day",
        "C": "Forever",
        "D": "Day and night",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 12,
        "UUID": "6-1-12",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:9, what had the Lord commanded Joshua?",
        "A": "Be strong",
        "B": "Be of good courage",
        "C": "Do not be afraid",
        "D": "All of the above",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 13,
        "UUID": "6-1-13",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:10-11, whom did Joshua command to pass through the camp?",
        "A": "Twelve men whom he had appointed",
        "B": "Eleazar",
        "C": "The priests",
        "D": "The officers of the people",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 14,
        "UUID": "6-1-14",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:11, what did Joshua want the people to do before crossing over the Jordan?",
        "A": "Offer sacrifices to the Lord",
        "B": "Pack up their tents",
        "C": "Arm themselves",
        "D": "Prepare provisions for themselves",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 15,
        "UUID": "6-1-15",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:11, within how many days did Joshua command the officers to tell the people that they would cross over the Jordan?",
        "A": "One",
        "B": "Two",
        "C": "Three",
        "D": "Many",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 16,
        "UUID": "6-1-16",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:12-14, which of the following of the tribes did NOT receive land on the east side of the Jordan?",
        "A": "Gad",
        "B": "Ephraim",
        "C": "Mannasseh",
        "D": "Reuben",
        "Correct": "B"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 17,
        "UUID": "6-1-17",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:13, when addressing the tribes who received land on the east side of the Jordan how did Joshua describe Moses?",
        "A": "Father",
        "B": "The prophet",
        "C": "The lawgiver",
        "D": "The servant of the Lord",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 18,
        "UUID": "6-1-18",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:13, what did Joshua say that God was giving the three tribes who received land on the east side of the Jordan?",
        "A": "Blessings",
        "B": "Turmoil",
        "C": "Rest",
        "D": "Many children",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 19,
        "UUID": "6-1-19",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:14, who from the three tribes who received land on the east side of the Jordan were to cross over the Jordan?",
        "A": "Their families",
        "B": "Their mighty men of valor",
        "C": "The young men",
        "D": "The women",
        "Correct": "B"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 20,
        "UUID": "6-1-20",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:15, when did Joshua say the three tribes possessing land east of the Jordan could return to their land?",
        "A": "When the Lord had given their brethren rest",
        "B": "After seven days",
        "C": "When their brethren had taken possession of the land",
        "D": "Both A and C",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 21,
        "UUID": "6-1-21",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:16, in response to Joshua, what did the people say that they would do?",
        "A": "All that Joshua commanded",
        "B": "Cross over the Jordan",
        "C": "Worship the Lord",
        "D": "Fight against Jericho",
        "Correct": "A"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 22,
        "UUID": "6-1-22",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:16, in response to Joshua, where did the people say that they would go?",
        "A": "To Jericho",
        "B": "Over the Jordan",
        "C": "To Gilgal",
        "D": "Wherever Joshua sent them",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 23,
        "UUID": "6-1-23",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:17, whom did the people say they had heeded in all things?",
        "A": "Aaron",
        "B": "Joshua",
        "C": "Eleazar",
        "D": "Moses",
        "Correct": "D"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 24,
        "UUID": "6-1-24",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 1:18, what did the people say would be the punishment for whoever rebelled against Joshua’s command?",
        "A": "They would be cut off from the people ",
        "B": "They would be cut off from the Lord",
        "C": "They would be put to death",
        "D": "They would not receive an inheritance in the land",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 1,
        "Number": 25,
        "UUID": "6-1-25",
        "Question": " In Joshua chapter 1, how many times did God tell Joshua to “be strong and of good courage”?",
        "A": "One",
        "B": "Two",
        "C": "Three",
        "D": "Four",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
    { 
        "Book": 6,
        "Chapter": 2,
        "Number": 1,
        "UUID": "6-2-1",
        "Question": " According to Joshua 2:1, how many men did Joshua send out from Acacia Grove to spy secretly?",
        "A": "One",
        "B": "Two",
        "C": "Seven",
        "D": "Twelve",
        "Correct": "C"
    },
]